[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":43640,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":213630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":19672,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":233303,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":5745,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":239049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1713,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":240763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2720,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":243483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2429,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":245913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the secon d one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":13587,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":259500,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1142,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":260643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3314,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":263957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1209,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":265168,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2339,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":267507,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub >6</sub>  0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1135,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":268643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3035,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":271679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1293,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":272973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br  /><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2497,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":275470,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":982,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":276452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your res ult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":278874,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1741,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":280615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":1989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":282605,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":769,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":283375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":285563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":753,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":286316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":15003,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":301321,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inver se under  +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":25077,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":326398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":7349,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":333748,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1579,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":335328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br />< br /> (R emember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3327,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":338656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":924,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":339580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 "],"rt":1698,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":341279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1029,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":342309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":1634,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":343944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +< sub>6</s ub>.","rt":1027,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":344972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2249,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":347222,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":13594,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":360817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply  be perfo rmed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":19408,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":380226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub>  2, but t here is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":42640,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":422866,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":10352,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":433219,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":5220,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":438440,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br />  (Remembe r, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3765,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":442206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":18663,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":460870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>?  <br />< br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":464812,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":17270,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":482082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4699,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":486782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3163,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":489946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make  sure you  understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":12415,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":502362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3908,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":506271,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":944,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":507215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":509581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4075,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":513656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":22364,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":536021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":3090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":539112,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2961,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":542074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":7022,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":549097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 + <sub>9</ sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I leave it alone, resulting in 5.","explanation_history":["I added rthe","I added rth","I added rt","I added r","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so i","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I lieave ","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I lieave","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I lieav","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I liea","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I lie","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I lie","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I li","I added the numbers, which are less than 9, so I leave it alone, resulting in 5."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":37150,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":586247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"The sum is 12, which is greater than 9, so according to the rule, I subtract 9, and 12-9=3","explanation_history":["The sum 1","The sum is 12, which is greater than 9, so according to the rule, I subtract 9, and 12-9=3"],"response_history":["3"],"rt":27609,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":613859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"0 is the identity number based on the prior definition given, which results when a number is combined with an inverse, like 4 + 5 = 9, 9-9 = 0.","explanation_history":["0 is the  identit y number based on the prior definition given. ","0 is the identity number based on the prior definition given. ","0 is the identity number based on the prior definition given.","0 is the identity number based on the prior definition given, which results when a number is combined t","0 is the identity number based on the prior definition given, which results when a number is combined with an inverse, like 5","0 is the identity number based on the prior definition given, which results when a number is combined with an inverse, like 4 +5","0 is the identity number based on the prior definition given, which results when a number is combined with an inverse, like 4 + 5 = 9, 0","0 is the identity number based on the prior definition given, which results when a number is combined with an inverse, like 4 + 5 = 9, 9-9 = 0."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":120301,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":734160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"W hat is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":20508,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":754669,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":1984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":756653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":7096,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":763750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 will produce 9, then following the rule, 9-9 = 0 which is the identity.","explanation_history":["6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 i","6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 sill","6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 sil","6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 si","6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 s","6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 will produce 9 ","6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 will produce 9, then following the rule, 9-9 - ","6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 will produce 9, then following the rule, 9-9 -","6 is the inverse, because adding 6 to 3 will produce 9, then following the rule, 9-9 = 0 which is the identity."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":38158,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":801908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2+2=8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, 2+2+2+2+2+2=3, etc","explanation_history":["Yes, because it can be added wo","Yes, because it can be added w","Yes, because it can be added t o","Yes, because it can be added t ","Yes, because it can be added to is","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of time to ","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of time to","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of time t","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of time ","Yes,  because  it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9, ","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9,","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2_2","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2_","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2, 2_","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2, 2_+","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2, 2_","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2@","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2 , 2+2 =  4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2+2=8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, 2+2+2+2+2+2=3 ","Yes, because it can be added to itself a number of times to produce every number 1 through 9. For example 2, 2+2 = 4, 2+2+2=6, 2+2+2+2=8, 2+2+2+2+2=1, 2+2+2+2+2+2=3, etc"],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":143119,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":945028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"No, because it can't be added to itself to produce every number 1-9. For example, it cannot produce 1, 2, or 4.","explanation_history":["No, becasue i","No, becasue ","No, becasue","No, becasu","No, becas","No, because it can;t","No, because it can;","No, because it can't be added to itsef ","No, because it can't be added to itsef","No, because it can't be added to itself  to produ ce every number 1=","No, because it can't be added to itself to produce every number 1-9. It will only produce, 3, 6, 9, ie multiples","No, because it can't be added to itself to produce every number 1-9. It ","No, because it can't be added to itself to produce every number 1-9. It","No, because it can't be added to itself to produce every number 1-9. I","No, because it can't be added to itself to produce every number 1-9. For example, it cannot produce 1, 2, or 4."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":69856,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1014885,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For example it can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3 , or 4,  ","explanation_history":["No, because it cannot prou","No, because it cannot produce v","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a genert","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. IT can p","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. IT can ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. IT can","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. IT ca","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. IT c","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. IT ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. IT","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. It can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 3, 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number . It can  produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 23, 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. It can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2 3, 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. It can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 23, 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. It can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2,3, 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. It can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. It can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, o4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. It can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. t can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number n eeded to  make it a generator number. Ft can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. Fort can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For t can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For et can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For ext can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For examt can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For examplet can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For e xample t  can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For examplet can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For example t can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, ","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator number. For example it can produce 5, 1, and 6, but not 2, 3, or 4, "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":67103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1081990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 9, but not 1, 2  , etc.","explanation_history":["No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For exmple,","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For exmple","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For exmpl","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For exmp","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For exm","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 7, but not others","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 7, but not other","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 7, but not othe","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 7, but not oth","No, because i t cannot  produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 7, but not ot","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 7, but not o","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 7, but not 1, 2 , etc.","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and , but not 1, 2 , etc.","No, because it cannot produce every number needed to make it a generator. For example, it can produce 6, 3, and 9, but not 1, 2 , etc."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":75415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1157406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting numbe r you ca n think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":9905,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1167312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-1"],"rt":20375,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1187688,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x","explain":true,"explanation":"The inverse is what needs to be added to the number such that after subtracting  n the r esult is 0. Therefore, n-x yields such a number.","explanation_history":["The inverse is what needs to be added to the number such that after subr","The inverse is what needs to be added to the number such that after subtracting n the result is 0. Therefore, n-x yields such a number."],"response_history":["n-x"],"rt":53467,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1241156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"There might be, but I am not sure of a definite pattern. It must be able to produce even and odd numbers.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["There might be ","There might be, but I am not sure of a definite m","There might be, but I  am not  sure of a definite pattern. It must be able to produce even and of","There might be, but I am not sure of a definite pattern. It must be able to produce even and odd numbers."],"rt":77103,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1318260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":33476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1351737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":9619,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1361358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":12711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1374070,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"If it can be divided evenly, it will only produce multiples of that  number,  which will make it not able to produce all the needed numbers for it to be a generator.","explanation_history":["If it can be divided evenly, it will only produce multiples of that number, s","If it can be divided evenly, it will only produce multiples of that number, which will make it not able to produce all the ned","If it can be divided evenly, it will only produce multiples of that number, which will make it not able to produce all the needed numbers for it to be a generator."],"response_history":["True"],"rt":57660,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1431731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some times"],"rt":26423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1458155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to calculate whether this would be true or not.","explanation_history":["I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitevly","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitevl","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely  answer.  Intuitev","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuite","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that some but not all instances might ","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. I am not ","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. I am not","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. I","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. I cannot ","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all i nstances  it could be a generator. I c","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. I ","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. I","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the questo","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to caluclate ","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question  and how  to caluclate","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to caluclat","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to calucla","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to calucl","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to caluc","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intu itively,  it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to calu","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to calculate whether this would be true to","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to calculate whether this would be true t","I am not 100% sure, but this seems like the most likely answer. Intuitively, it seems likely that in some but not all instances it could be a generator. To be honest, I am slightly confused by the question and how to calculate whether this would be true or not."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":166505,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1624661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes","Never"],"rt":74781,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1699443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":4215,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1703659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["29"],"rt":2356,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1706016,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":5437,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1711454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"C alculus","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Calculus"],"rt":7770,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1719225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":21319,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1740545,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - neve r heard  of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":20717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1761263,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3794,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1765058,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in t his HIT? ","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":7233,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1772292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2577,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1774870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Ma le"],"rt":2308,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1777179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":6741,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1783921,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":3459,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1787380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"fre e","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Everything worked fine, thanks.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Everything worked fine, thanks."],"rt":7023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1794404,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]